monstrous.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy policy

Monstrous.com is concerned about your privacy. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. 

This Privacy Policy covers Monstrous.com's treatment of personal information that Monstrous.com collects when you use the Monstrous.com site, and when you use Monstrous.com's services. This policy also covers Monstrous.com's treatment of any personal information that Monstrous.com's business partners share with Monstrous.com or that Monstrous.com may collect on a partner's site. 

This policy [celebrity porn](http://my-celebrity-porn.tumblr.com/) does not apply to the practices of companies that Monstrous.com does not own or control, or to people that Monstrous.com does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and[celebrities sex videos](http://www.arinum.com/celebrities-sex-videos/) Use**

  * Monstrous.com collects personal information when you register to our Forum, when you subscribe to Monstrous.com newsletter, when you use Monstrous.com products or services, when you visit Monstrous.com pages. Monstrous.com may also receive personal information from our business partners. 
  * When you register with Monstrous.com, we ask for your email address. Once you register with Monstrous.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. 
  * Monstrous.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser cookie information and the page you requested. 
  * Monstrous.com uses information for three general purposes: [celebrity gossip](http://thecelebrityauction.co/) to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, and to provide traffic statistics to our webmaster. None of the statistics reported include personal information about any Monstrous.com user.
  * This website may utilize certain services provided by DoubleClick, Inc. (“DoubleClick”).  For further information concerning DoubleClick’s privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its [propecia online](http://www.eduardogellner.de/propecia-online/) services, please go to <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/>

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

  * Monstrous.com will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone. 
  * Monstrous.com may send personal information about you to other companies or people when: 
    * We have your consent to share the information; 
    * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; 
    * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Monstrous.com to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the [Lesbian Porn](http://www.realpicsonly.com/category/Lesbian/) personal information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);

**Cookies**

  * Monstrous.com may set and access Monstrous.com cookies on your computer. 
  * Monstrous.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Monstrous.com's cookies. 

**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**

Monstrous.com gives [milf porn](http://my-milf-porn.tumblr.com/) you the ability to delete your subscription to our services at any time. 

**Changes to this[nude celebs](http://best-naked-celebrities.tumblr.com/) Privacy Policy**

Monstrous.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
